声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：sealovemoon  憨妹 闲逛
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
哇哦! 轻点  蠢驴
Ow! Easy, jackass.
要我轻点就别再抱怨 我得给你换绷带
You want it easy, quit moaning. I got to change these bandages.
好  但别把我的皮也扯下来了
Try not taking my skin off with them.
我把你映衬得怎样  Quinn医生?  缓解你良心上的不安了?
How'd I score the house call, Dr.Quinn? Trying to ease your conscience?
我良心上没什么不安  谢谢
My conscience is fine, thanks.
当然  有什么事情会让你内疚?
Of course, what have you got to feel guilty about?
我是说  你让那个该死的阿拉伯人折磨我  自己却站在一旁观看
I mean, you just let that damn Arab torture me.Stood by and watched.
现在又想修补你我之间的关系  给自己买去天堂的飞机票?
Now you figure you'll patch me up and buy you a ticket into heaven?
你在这儿的唯一原因是...
Only reason you're here...
我在这儿是因为  没有一个人想和你扯上关系
I'm here because no one else wants anything to do with you.
她会的
She does.
自己换绷带去
Change your own bandages.
找人呢?  还是欣赏风景?
Looking for someone,or just admiring the view?
Sayid独自离开已经两天了
It's been two days since Sayid took off on his own.
我一直期待着能看到他回来
I keep thinking I'm gonna see him.
等到他找到要找的东西后  他会回来的...
He'll come when he's found what he's looking for,
-那个法国人的求救传输信号  -他不是去找东西
-The French transmission.  -He wasn't looking for anything.
他离开是因为之前发生的事
He left because of what happened.
-是因为他自己的行为  -那是个意外
-for what he did  -It was an accident.
意外却发生在你折磨人的时候 Jack
Well, accidents happen when you torture people, Jack.
Sayid是个训练有素的军人  Kate
Sayid's a trained soldier, Kate.
他会照顾好自己
He can take care of himself.
有人吗?
Hello?
把他赶出去!  他在喝我们的水
Ew! Get him out of there! He's drinking our water.
那儿怎么了?
What's going on out there?
你知道  和往常一样
You know, the usual.
为了点小事情争来争去
People yelling at each other.
医生  你觉得这是...  这是...
Doc, what do you think this is, this...
这皮疹?  很糟是吗?  是那种热带病?
...this rash? It's bad, right? Some kind of a tropical disease?
-是麻疹  -那是什么?
-It's hives.  -What's that?
毒葛之类的东西吗?
Is that like poison ivy?
这是一种很普通的皮疹  有时候是由于热和压力引起的
It's a common rash, sometimes brought on by heat and stress.
放松就行了
Just try to relax.
-都弄干净了  -好
-It'll clear up.  -Right.
不要老想着它
Try to keep your mind off it.
好的  这是什么?  芦荟吗?
Okay.What is that? Is that like aloe?
用来防晒的吗?  还是其它用途?
Isn't that for sunburn or something?
"不要老想着它"?
"Try to keep your mind off it"?
那家伙除了给自己增加压力  还能干什么?
What else has that guy got to do but stress?
我事情已经够多了  没必要连忧郁症也治吧
I have enough without having to treat hypochondriacs.
是  那正是我要说的
That's like my point, man.
大家都备受煎熬
We're all fried.
我是说
I mean
你去看过那儿的人了吗?
have you taken a look at everybody out there?
每个人都很焦虑
Everybody's way tense.
老兄  我想说的是  我们最好能干点什么...
Dude, I'm just saying,it... it'd be sweet if we could have...
我不知道  至少干点什么
I don't know, something to do.
我们都还活着  Hurley
We're surviving here, Hurley.
那才是我要干的事  保证每个人都活着
And that's my main concern, is keeping us alive.
事情可能会变得更糟
Things could be worse.
怎么变?
How?
Alex在哪?
Where is Alex?
什么?
What?
你是谁?
Who are you?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you are talking about.
Alex在哪?
Where is Alex?
求你  不要....
Please, let's not...
-Alex在哪?  -我不认识什么Alex
-Where is Alex?  -I don't know any Alex.
住手!
Stop!
你要我住手  Flahn?
那就回答我的问题
我可以折磨你一整天
我向你保证  我们已经了解了事情真相
但我要你承认
你就不会再遭受任何痛苦
And all the pain will stop.
你的什叶派教徒朋友向我们暗示  你参与了爆炸事件
Your Shiite friends have already implicated you in the bombing.
是你把爆炸装置安装在政党总部  是不是?
You planted the device in the headquarters!
你杀了两个士兵!
You killed two soldiers!
承认吧
Confess it
承认的话  或许你可以保住你的小命  我们要你的手就够了
and perhaps it will only cost you your hands instead of your life.
他什么都不知道
He doesn't know anything.
-你的消息有错  -也许吧
-Your sources were wrong.  -Perhaps.
但那不是关键  是吧?
But that's really not the point, is it?
你在那儿把自己掌控的非常好
You handled yourself well in there.
是吗?
Did I?
我已经提交了你的调职申请  如果你仍想调职的话
I put in for your reassignment to intelligence division, If you still wish it.
是的  长官  非常想
Yes, sir. Very much so.
很好  只有我们两个人的时候  不用叫我"长官"
Good. But stop calling me "sir" when it's just the two of us.
你是我的上级指挥  Omar...至少现在还是
You're my superior officer, Omar.
在你未调职之前  我很高兴你这么叫
For now.And I'll enjoy it while it lasts.
那倒提醒了我  Sayid
That reminds me,
除了你越来越重的责任
in addition to your increased responsibilities,
官位的提升和你的能力很相称
a promotion is commensurate with your move.
如果你不会怀念当一位审讯官的话
That is, if you won't miss being a communications officer.
我愿意作出那样的牺牲
I am willing to make that sacrifice.
很好
Good.
这是什么?
Yo. What's this?
在丛林里找到的  一定是飞机上掉下来的
They must have fallen from the plane.
你们昨晚在丛林里干什么?
What are you doing in the jungle at night?
打猎的好时间
Best time to hunt.
Ethan有些经验
Ethan here has some experience.
他发现了一些足迹  看起来像兔子的或其它啮齿动物
He spotted tracks that might be a rabbit or some other rodent.
啮齿动物  妙极了
Rodent. Yum.
我想人们已经吃厌了野猪肉
People are getting tired of boar meat.
你说对了
You got that right.
好  我看看
All right, well,I'll take a look at these,
看有没用的着东西
See if there's anything useful.
好
Okay.
Locke先生
Mr. Locke.
你还要回去打猎吗?
Are you going back out to hunt?
再打一会儿
For a bit.
我可以一起去吗?  我是说...
Can I go with you? I mean,
我想向你学习怎么做你做的事
I just want to learn how to do what you do.
Walt!
我只是...  我只是和Locke先生谈谈关于....
I was... I was talking to Mr. Locke about...
我知道你在干什么  不可能的事  回到床上来
I know what you're doing. Not gonna happen, man. Get back to bed.
老兄...
Whoa, dude...
请听我说!
Please just listen to me!
我说了很多遍了  我不认识Alex!
I keep telling you I don't know who Alex is!
我是一个飞机失事的幸存者
I'm a survivor of a plane crash.
偶然在海滩边发现了这根绳索
I found the wire on the beach.
就沿着绳索走过来了
I followed it.
我想这或许和...
I thought it might have something to do with
和我们接收到的求救信号有关
a transmission we picked up on a receiver.
一个留言  一个求救信号
A recording, a mayday
是一个法国女子的声音  已经重复循环了16年了
with a French woman repeating on a loop for 16 years.
16年
Sixteen years.
真有那么长吗?
Has it really been that long?
你...
You.
你会碰巧收到了我的求救信号?
You just happened to hear my distress call?
我知道你是什么样的人
I know what you are.
Rousseau
-你怎么知道我的名字?  -我读的
-How do you know my name?  -I read it.
那儿  在夹克衫上
There, on the jacket.
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
那些电池...
Those batteries
还不足以产生如此多的能量
wouldn't be able to produce enough power
来传输一个历经这么多年的求救信号
to transmit your distress call all these years.
是其它地方传输的信号
Broadcasts from somewhere else.
但被他们控制了
But they control it now.
他们?
They?
你
You.
以及其它像你一样的人
And the others like you.
我不知道你对我怎么想的  我已经告诉过你了
I... I don't know who you think I am. I've already told you.
-我不是....  -Sayid?
-I am not...  -Sayid?
你怎么知道我的...
How...?
我的名字在我的夹克衫上  你的名字在你带来的信上
My name was on a jacket. Yours is on the envelope you carry.
她是谁?
Who is she?
照片中的女子
The woman in the photographs.
Nadia
她叫Nadia
Her name is Nadia.
我们不能直接把 Noor Abed Jazeem 和爆炸事件联系起来
We cannot tie Noor Abed Jazeem to the bombing,
但我们知道她效忠什么样的人
but we know her sympathies.
她是一个众人皆知的  库尔德人和什叶派起义者的联系人
She's a known associate of Kurdish and Shiite insurgents.
你认为她知道谁策划了  这起爆炸事件?
She knows who orchestrated the bombing?
我的朋友  那就是你要去搞清楚的
That, my friend,is exactly what you will find out.
Noor Abed Jazeem
我要问你些问题
I'm going to ask you some questions.
如果你拒绝合作  我会对你动手  明白吗?
If you refuse to cooperate, I'm going to hurt you.
没人叫我Noor, Sayid
Nobody calls me Noor, Sayid.
你们所有人都应该知道的
You of all people should know that.
什么?
What?
你不记得我了?
You don't remember me?
曾在操场上把你推进泥浆里的  小女孩现在变化有这么大吗?
Am I so different from the girl in the schoolyard who used to push you in the mud?
Nadia
还有你妈妈告诉我妈妈  "为什么你非要选中小Sayid?"
And your mother would tell my mother, "Why must you pick on little Sayid?"
我回答  "因为他忽视我"
And I'd answer, "Because he ignores me."
你得到大家足够的关注  家里又有钱还有...
You had enough attention, with your family's wealth and...
你很迷人
your charm.
很少有小孩子关注这种事情
Such things matter little to children.
但你总是显得很老成  是不是  Sayid?
But then, you always were older than your years,weren't you, Sayid?
我还没老成到能理解  "把我推到泥浆里"算是一种喜欢的暗示
Not old enough to understand that being pushed was a sign of affection.
如今你背叛了你的国家
Now you're a traitor to your country.
告诉我你对爆炸事件了解多少  Nadia
Tell me what you know about the bombing, Nadia.
告诉我  否则  我发誓我一定会伤害你
Tell me, or I swear I will hurt you.
我知道  Sayid
Hmm. Oh, I know, Sayid.
这不是我第一次被共和卫队审问了
This is not my first interrogation by the Republican Guard.
这就是他们在我身上扑浓酸的地方
This is where they burned me with acid.
他们用钻头在我的掌心钻孔
They pierced my hands with a drill.
你想看看我的脚底吗?
Would you like to see the soles of my feet?
那是他们把皮扯去的地方
Where they flayed the skin off?
这些都是你的朋友的手艺
These are handiworks of your friends.
我曾经却还发誓效忠这些人
The people you swear allegiance to.
如果你是清白的  我很抱歉
If you were innocent, I'm sorry.
但这起爆炸事件事关重大
But this bombing is a different matter.
-Nadia...  -干吧  Sayid
-Nadia...  -Go on, Sayid.
干你的工作
Do your work.
我什么都不会跟你说的
I'm not going to tell you anything.
那我就动手了
Then I'm going to hurt you.
我知道
I know.
你有子弹疤痕
You have a bullet wound.
我曾是个军人
I was a soldier.
曾是?
You were?
现在还是?
And are you still?
那已经是很久前的事了
It was a long time ago.
多讲些她的事
Tell me more about her,the woman.
Nadia
Alex... 他是谁?
Alex... who is he?
我无聊死了!
I'm bored.
我可以带Vincent去海边吗?
Can I take Vincent to the beach?
我过会儿带你去  小子
Um... I'll take you later.
我处理点事情
I'm in the middle of something.
但实在没事可干
But there's nothing to do.
你得想些事做做  知道我的意思吗?
Well, you got to figure out stuff to do.
你得给自己找些娱乐节目
You got to find a way to entertain yourself.
拜托  拜托  我知道我看到了
Come on. Come on. I know I saw it.
好的
Yes.
Hurley...
等等  伙计  我很忙
Hold on, man. I'm busy.
老兄  我能借下这个吗?
Dude, can I borrow this?
-什么?  -谢谢
-What?  -Thanks, man.
Hurley  你要干什么?
What are you doing?
那么说你收到了我的信号
So you heard my transmission,
过来找我  寻求答案
Came looking for me, for answers.
我不知道你还活着
I didn't know you were alive.
还在说谎
Still lying.
-我没说谎  -说谎!
-I'm not lying.  -Lies!
像那些什么飞机失事啦  你存活了 还有其它幸存者啦
Like this plane crash that you survived.There were others?
-40多个人  -那为什么你会独自一个人?
-More than 40.  -Then why are you alone?
-我离开了他们  -为什么?
-I left them.  -Why?
有...
There was...
我干了一些...
I did something.
一些我感到羞耻的事
Something I'm ashamed of.
Nadia... 你也离开了她?
And Nadia... you left her too?
她不在飞机上
She wasn't on the plane.
她死了
She's dead.
因为我
Because of me.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我给你看些东西
I want to show you something.
看  汇合处在这
See, this junction here
把一部分水引导到几个悬空的盆子
reroutes some of the spring's water flow into suspended basins.
水从几个洞流出来  你就能洗澡了
Pop in some holes, you got showers.
这样就可以把饮用水隔离开来了
You keep the drinking water separate.
这是... 你画的?
This is... You drew this?
早些时候我是个艺术家
I was an artist in a previous life.
我还以为你是个建筑师
I thought you were in construction.
我是的  我是说  你知道  我过去是  说来故事长了
I am. I mean I was. Long story.
Jack!
Hurley对某样东西很激动 说我们应该过去看看
Hurley's worked up about something. Said we should see it.
欢迎...
Welcome...
来到第一届...
...to the first and...
也希望是最后一届
...hopefully last,
孤岛高尔夫公开赛
Island Open.
什么?
What?
现在有两个洞
It's two holes, for now.
3个标准杆  无须等待
Three par, and no waiting.
Hurley  你建了个高尔夫球场?
Hurley... You built a golf course?
那些富佬向来飞到热带岛屿打球
Rich idiots fly to tropical islands to whack balls around.
我们有很多事要做  老兄
All the stuff we got to deal with, man,
原来你的时间都浪费在这儿了?
this is what you've been wasting time on?
伙计  听着
Dudes, listen.
我们的生活糟透了
Our lives suck.
每个人的神经都绷的紧紧的
Nerves are stretched to the max.
我是说  我们迷失在了一个岛上
I mean, we're lost on an island,
躲避野猪还有怪兽...
running from boars and monsters...
还有反常的北极熊!
Freakin' polar bears!
北极熊?
Polar bears?
你没听说北极熊?
You didn't hear about the polar bear?
听着  我要说的是如果  我们真被困在这儿了
If we're stuck here,
光活着也是不办法啊
then just surviving's not gonna cut it.
我们需要放松  你明白吗?
We need some kind of relief.
我们得找些我们可以...
We need some way that we can...
你知道  娱乐方式
...you know, have fun.
对  娱乐
That's right, fun.
否则  傻等着另一件坏事的发生  我们会疯掉的
Or we're gonna go crazy, waiting for the next bad thing to happen.
这是个音乐盒  但坏掉了
It's a music box, but it's broken.
已经...
Has been...
有很长一段时间了
...for a long time.
这是我爱人送给我的 作为结婚周年纪念的礼物
It was a gift from my love for our anniversary.
你是说Alex
You mean Alex.
Robert
在这儿的头几年 这东西成了我最大的安慰
It was such a comfort to me the first few years here.
我可以帮你修好
I could fix it for you.
如果你能给我的手松绑  我能帮你检查一下
I could take a look at it if you freed my hands.
我对机械类的东西很在行
I'm fairly good with mechanical things.
我需要我的手...
I'll need my hands.
照片后面写的是什么?
What is written on the back of your photograph?
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
她写的还是你写的?
Did she write it, or did you?
或许你不想告诉我  因为有太多的痛苦
Perhaps you don't want to tell me because it causes too much pain.
Rousseau...
你不必那么做的
You don't need to do that.
-这是个问题  老兄  -是的
-This is a problem, man.  -Yeah.
我是说  我知道该怎么做  但...
I mean, I know what I'd do, but...
该你叫球了
...it's gotta be your call.
好
Okay.
给我7号铁头球棒
Give me a 7 iron.
知道了
Got it.
抬起头来!
Heads up over there!
-没有机会的!  -不要打飞了!
-No chance!  -Don't blow it!
你打不到我们周围的!
You won't get anywhere near us!
医生!  你在这儿呀
Hey! Doc!There you are.
有人说你朝这边来了
Somebody said you went this way.
听着  我的皮疹开始扩散了  有釉子那么大了
Listen, that rash of mine is starting to spread. It's like the size of a grape...
你们在干什么?
What are you guys doing?
打高尔夫?
Are you playing golf?
是的
Yeah.
我也能玩吗?
Can I play?
我为镇静剂的事道歉
Sorry about the sedative.
要移动你  这是我能想到的唯一的安全的办法
It was the only safe way for me to move you.
你提议要帮我修音乐盒
You offered to fix my music box.
在我对你干了那么多事之后  打你  刺激你
After all I've done to you. Striking you, shocking you.
为什么?
Why?
你想要我修你的音乐盒  还是不想?
Do you want me to fix your music box, or don't you?
是的  请
Yes, please.
那我想知道你的名字  你的名
Then I want to know your name. Your first name.
Danielle
我叫Danielle
My name is Danielle.
你是怎么来到这个岛上的 Danielle?
And how did you come to be on this island, Danielle?
我们是一支科考队的
We were part of a science team.
用枪武装的科考队
A science team armed with rifles.
-Robert也在队里吗?  -是的
-Was Robert on the team?  -Yes.
还有Alex... 他也是?
And Alex, was he, too?
通讯设备坏了的时候  我们的船离开塔西提岛已经三天了
Our vessel was three days out of Tahiti when our instruments malfunctioned.
那是个晚上
It was night.
那暴雨...
The storm...
那咆哮...
The sounds...
船只被甩到了岩石上
The ship slammed into rocks,
冲到了地面  船体破裂到了无法修补的程度
ran aground,the hull breached beyond repair.
所以...
So...
我们扎了营
...we made camp.
找到了这个临时庇护所
Dug out this temporary shelter.
临时的
Temporary.
我们在这儿活了将近两个月
Nearly two months we survived here.
两个月  然后....
Two months before...
你的求救信号... 我接收到的...
Your distress signal. The message I heard.
你说  "它把他们都杀了"
You said "It killed them all."
我们从黑岩那儿回来
We were coming back from the black rock.
是他们
It was them.
-他们是携带者  -谁是携带者?
-They were the carriers.  -Who were the carriers?
其他人
The others.
其他什么人?
What others?
"黑岩"是什么?
What is the black rock?
你在岛上看到其他人了?
Have you seen other people on this island?
没有
No.
但我听到了
But I hear them.
在丛林里面
Out there in the jungle.
他们低声细语
They whisper.
你认为我疯了
You think I'm insane.
我想你独处的太久了
I think you've been alone for too long.
我很抱歉  我只能找到这些了
I'm sorry. This is all I could find.
我会再找找  稍后给你带些水果
I'll try and bring you some fruit later on.
准备说了?
Are you ready to talk?
那取决于...
That depends on
...你想谈什么  Sayid
what you'd like to talk about, Sayid.
书?
Books?
天气?
Weather?
我被锁在这地牢  几周没见过书和天气了
Since I've seen neither locked in this cell for weeks,
恐怕我们的交谈会很不顺畅
I'm afraid my conversation will suffer.
有两个嫌疑犯在我们的监管下
We have two suspects in custody.
看这些照片
Have a look at these photographs.
你所要做的就是点头而已
All you need to do is nod.
如果你能证明自己愿意合作
If you prove you're willing to cooperate,
我想我能说服他们放了你的
I think I can get them to free you.
那样我就再也期待不到这样的"访问"了
Then I won't have these visits to look forward to anymore.
这不是个游戏  Nadia
This isn't a game, Nadia.
你却还在玩  Sayid
Yet you keep playing it, Sayid.
假装一些事(骗我)  我知道你不是
Pretending to be something I know you're not.
你不会相信的
You'll never believe this.
你终于知道怎么系鞋带了?
You learned how to tie your shoes?
有趣  洞里有个家伙建了个高尔夫球场
Funny. Someone at the caves built a golf course.
-你很兴奋?  -真的  一个高尔夫球场
-Are you high?  -Seriously, a golf course.
显然  Jack他们现在在一块儿玩
Jack's playing right now.
-Jack?  打高尔夫?  -我听说是这样
-Jack? Is golfing?  -That's what I hear.
我不知道你们怎么想  但我要去看看
I don't know about you, but I'm gonna check this out.
等等我  笨蛋
Wait for me, bonehead.
医生打高尔夫
Doctor playing golf.
好小伙啊  我现在是什么都听说了
Whoo! Boy howdy, now I've heard everything.
还会发生什么  偷吃炸面圈?
What's next, cop eating a donut?
如果你要来  说就行了
If you want to come, you should say.
我不屑一顾  雀斑女 我不热衷于集体活动
Think I'll pass on that, Freckles. Not big on crowds.
让我们面对吧  我也对人群不敢兴趣
And let's face it, crowd's not too hot on me, either.
一个接一个被遗弃
One outcast to another,
我在想我们得多努力一点
I'd think about making more of an effort.
建议收到
Duly noted.
你看?
You see?
有些东西可以被修好
Some things can be fixed.
谢谢
Thank you.
太感谢你了
Thank you so much.
Danielle  请你放我回去
Danielle, please let me go.
回去?
Go?
回到我跟你说过的人群中去
Back to the people I told you about.
你不能回去  你得呆在这儿
You can't. You have to stay.
-不安全  -不安全?  什么不安全?
-It's not safe.  -Not safe? What's not safe?
你需要我  你不能走
You need me. You can't leave.
你要去哪儿?
Where are you going?
如果我们幸运  是其中一只熊
If we're lucky, it's one of the bears.
如果我们幸运?
If we're lucky?
或许是那东西
It might be that thing out there.
那怪物
The monster.
根本没什么怪物
There's no such thing as monsters.
你得把她处理掉
You have to execute her.
什么?
What?
那女子什么消息都没给我们
The Jazeem woman has given us nothing.
这会让其它人觉得我们不会逼供
This will send a message to others who will not talk.
再多给我些时间
I just need more time with her.
已经给你一个多月了  Sayid
You have had more than a month, Sayid.
现在把她带到外面  一枪毙了她  否则我来做
Now bring her outside and shoot her, or I will.
有问题吗?
Is this a problem?
没  没问题
No. It's not a problem.
很好
Good.
你今天给我带了什么?
What did you bring me today?
戴上
Put it on.
你要伤害我 Sayid?
Are you going to hurt me, Sayid?
老兄  我想你打进了
Ugh! Dude, I think you stuck it.
好运啊  好运
Lucky, lucky.
这东西有女子队的吗?
This thing have a ladies' team?
-你怎么来了?  -来了一会了
-Hey, how did you show up?  -A while ago.
我差点认不出你了
I almost didn't recognize you.
-你笑了  -我得向前看
-You're smiling.  -I have to watch that.
你怎么想出这点子的?
So, how'd you come up with this?
不是我  都是Hurley弄的
Wasn't me. It was all Hurley.
为了让每个人感到安全  我都快疯了
I've been going crazy to make everyone feel safe.
我一直没睡好过  因为我想让每个人感到安全
I haven't been sleeping 'cause I want everyone to feel safe.
他建了个高尔夫球场
He builds a golf course,
每个人都感觉很安全
And everyone feels safe.
垃圾!  重来
Aw, crap! Do-over.
这是加击  加击
It's a Mulligan.
这是一项绅士运动  你得明白这个词  "加击"
A gentleman's sport. You got to get the words right.
爸爸
Dad.
过来  看这个
Hey. Check this out.
你想要... 让我  让我
You want to... Let me.
伙计  放开我!
Get away!
你把我一个人留在洞里
You left me alone at the caves.
什么?  我让你和Claire在一起
What?  I left you with Claire.
她在睡觉
She's sleeping.
儿子  我... 我很抱歉
Oh, man, I'm... I'm sorry.
我只是...  我也刚过来
I just... I just got caught up.
真的很抱歉 Walt  我把事情弄得一团糟
I'm really sorry, Walt. I screwed up.
我补偿给你  想玩吗?
I'll make it up to you. Hey, you wanna play?
不了  其他人也在等
Nah. There's other people waiting.
不  这你不用担忧  他们不会介意的  想挥一杆吗?
They won't mind. You want to take a swing?
Michael  该你了  过来吧
Michael, it's your shot. You're up.
好  酷  那我们以后再玩  好吗?
Okay, cool. Uh, so we'll play later, okay?
把枪放下  Danielle
Put the gun down, Danielle.
放地上
Put it down on the ground.
不要
Don't.
这儿由我带过去
I'll take it from here.
什么... 发生什么事了?
What... what's going on?
门外40米处
Forty meters outside this door,
有辆供货车  马上就要开了
there's a supply truck that will be leaving.
他们不会检查这辆车的外出
They don't check them on the way out.
进来的时候才会检查
躲到里面  不管用什么  一定要把自己遮盖起来
Cover yourself any way you can.
30分钟内  他们赶不到市里
They won't reach the city for 30 minutes.
你有足够的时间跳车  然后藏起来
That's enough time to hide.
和我一起去
Come with me.
我不能
I can't.
逃避
Desertion.
他们会杀了我全家的
They would kill my family.
我没有你那样的勇气
I don't have your courage.
你的勇气比你知道的要多
You have more than you know.
Nadia  你得走了
Nadia, you have to go.
Sayid?
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
不要
Don't.
警卫!
Guard!
Sayid!
现在你得和我一起走了!  他们会杀了你的!
Now you have to come with me! They'll kill you!
不  你逃走了  你偷了我的枪然后杀了他
No. You escaped, you stole my gun,and you shot him.
又打了我
And then you shot me.
Sayid!
拿住
Take it.
求你了  Nadia
Please, Nadia.
拿住  走吧
Take it and go.
拜托了  我并不想伤害你
Please,I don't wish to hurt you.
已经伤害了
You already have.
不要
Don't.
撞针已经被拿掉了
The firing pin has been removed.
我打Robert的时候  他也不知道这已经没了
Robert didn't notice it was missing, either, when I shot him.
但你爱他
But you loved him.
-他病了  -病了?
-He was sick.  -Sick?
病夺去了他们的生命  一个接着一个
It took them... one after the other.
我无从选择
I had no choice.
他们都已经迷失了
They were already lost.
你杀了他们
You killed them.
如果我们被解救会发生什么事吗?
What would have happened if we were rescued?
我不允许那样的事情发生
I couldn't let that happen.
我不会!
I won't!
我没病
I'm not sick.
我知道
I know.
那为什么要杀了我?
Then why kill me?
我不能放你走
I can't let you go.
你不明白吗?
Don't you understand?
可以和人说说话  可以触摸...
To have someone to talk to...to touch.
"今生找不到我  来世会找到我的"
"You'll find me in the next life,if not in this one."
什么?
What?
写在Nadia照片后面的话
The writing on the back of Nadia's photograph.
我知道  等待一个人是什么感觉
I know what it's like to hold on to someone.
过去的7年  我一直在等待  为的就是一个希望
I've been holding on for seven years to just a thought.
一个渺茫的希望  希望在某个地方她还活着
A blind hope that somewhere she's still alive.
但是我越坚持
But the more I hold on,
我就越远离身边的人
the more I pull away from those around me.
离开这个岛的唯一的方法是...
The only way off this... this place,
是得到他们的帮助
is with their help.
和我一块儿去
Come with me.
没必要再孤独了  Danielle
You don't have to be alone, Danielle.
你们那些人
Your people,
你决意要回去的  那个地方的那些人
the ones you're determined to get back to.
看着他们
Watch them.
看的仔细些
Watch them closely.
Danielle!
Alex是谁?
Who is Alex?
Alex是我的孩子
Alex was my child.
伙计们  拜托
Guys, please.
我以前还从没在场上打过杆
I've never made par on a course before.
-不!  -老兄  真是狗屎运啊
-Ah! No!  -Dude, you were robbed.
乱说!  看到了吧?
Bollocks! See that?
好  Jack  该你了
Okay, Jack, it's up to you.
要打进的话  你得件夹克
Sink this, you get the blazer.
-不要有压力  -是  不要有压力
-No pressure.  -Yeah, no pressure.
5美圆  我赌他打进
Five bucks says he sinks it.
小子  你赌他赢我?
You betting against me?
抱歉  老兄  你和我一样是个蠢驴
Sorry, dude, But you're a duffer like me.
10美圆  我就压在你的赌注上
Make it ten.
我没现金  但我把晚饭压上  赌医生赢
I don't have any cash, but I'll bet my dinner on the doc.
我压两剂防晒油和一支手电筒  赌他输
I got two tubes of sunscreen and a flashlight says he chokes.
我赌他这边
I'll take that action.
是  是的  我也赌他
Yeah, me too.
你刚刚还赌Jack赢  傻蛋
You just bet on Jack, dumbass.
我们需要防晒油  公主
We need the sunscreen, princess.
你爸爸知道你来这了吗?
Does your father know you're here?
你能教我如何才能做到你那样吗?
Can you teach me how to do that?
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====